假设三台服务器的日志如下所示，其中数字
let's imagine three servers with logs
that looked like this where the numbers
我正在写的是该日志条目中命令的术语号，因此我们
I'm writing are the term numbers of the
command that's in that log entry so we
不在乎实际的命令是什么，然后我得到一个数字日志
don't really care what the actual
commands are then I got a number the log
插槽，因此，我们假设下一个学期大概是第六学期
slots and so let's imagine that the
presumably the the next term is term six
尽管您实际上无法从董事会上的证据中看出这一点
although you can't actually tell that
from looking the evidence on the board
但必须至少为六个或更多，让我们想象一下选择了服务器s3
but it must be at least six or greater
let's imagine that server s3 is chosen
作为第六学期的领导者，并且在s3的某个时刻，新领导者会想要
as the leader for term six and at some
point s3 the new leader is going to want
发送一个新的日志条目，所以我们假设它要发送第一个日志条目
to send out a new log entry so let's
suppose it wants to send out its first
每学期六个条目的日志条目，因此我们在考虑附加条目
log entry per term six so we're sort of
thinking about the append entries our
负责人将要发送的PC携带第一学期的日志条目
PCs that the leader is going to send out
to carry the first log entry for term
六个确实应该位于插槽13中，图2中的规则说
six really should be under slot thirteen
the rules in Figure two say that an
附加条目实际上是-以及客户端发送的命令
append entries are bc actually as - as
well as the command that the client sent
进入领导者，我们要在所有
in to the leader that we want to
replicate on the logs of all the
追随者那里有此追加条目RPC也包含此以前的日志
followers there's this append entries
RPC also contains this previous log
索引字段和上一个对数术语字段，以及当我们发送结束时
index field and a previous log term
field and when we're sending out an end
在这是我们领导应该输入的第一个条目的地方输入条目
pend entries for where this is the first
entry we're leaders supposed to put
有关前一个插槽的信息，发送新信息之前的插槽
information about the previous slot the
slot before the new information sending
因此，在这种情况下，上一个条目的对数索引为12，而
out so in this case the log index of the
previous entry is 12 and the term of the
领导者日志中用于上一个条目的命令是通过发送的
command in the leaders log for the
previous entry is by so sends out this
向追随者和追随者接受信息之前，
information to the followers
and the followers before they accept a
upend条目应该检查您是否知道他们已经收到
upend entries are supposed to check you
know they know they've received an
追加从此处开始的一些日志条目的条目以及它们的第一件事
append entries that for some log entries
that start here and the first thing they
要做的是检查接收者是否之前有过追踪者
do is check that there are previous the
receiving followers check that their
前一个日志条目与领导者所遵循的先前信息相匹配
previous log entry matches the previous
information that follow that the leader
发送出去，因此对于服务器来说，它当然与服务器不匹配，因此没有条目
sent out so for a server to of course it
doesn't match the server to has a entry
好的，但这是从学期开始的条目，而不是从第五回合开始的条目，因此
here all right but it's an entry from
term for not from turn five and so the
服务器二人将拒绝此追加条目并发送错误回复
server twos going to reject this append
entries and sort of send a false reply
后面的领导者和服务器甚至都没有东西，所以服务器
back leader and server one doesn't even
have anything here so server ones gonna
还拒绝领导者中的追加条目，到目前为止，
also reject the append entries in the
leader and so so far so good right the
在这一点上已经避免的可怕的事情是你知道
terrible thing that that has been
averted at this point is you know the
我们绝对不希望看到的坏事是服务器实际上卡住了
bad thing we absolutely don't want to
see is that server to actually stuck the
这里的新博客条目将本质上破坏归纳证明
new blog entry in here which would break
sort of inductive proofs essentially
方案图所依赖并隐藏了服务器两个实际
that the figure to scheme relies on and
hide the fact that server two actually
具有不同的日志，因此与其接受日志输入服务器这两个项目不同，
had a different log so instead of
accepting log entry server two projects
领导者看到的这个RPC是两次拒绝，领导者正在维护
this RPC the leader sees is two
rejections and leader is maintaining
下一个索引字段用于每个关注者，因此它具有下一个索引
this next index field one for each
follower so it has a next index for
服务器二和领导者有一个服务器的下一个索引大概是如果
server two and the leader has a next
index for server one presumably if the
如果服务器发送有关以下内容的信息，则应该在此之前说过：
should have said this before if the
server sending out information about
这里的插槽13必须表示服务器的下一个索引是针对两个
slot thirteen here that must mean that
the server's next index is for both of
这些其他服务器最初是13台，
these other servers this started out as
thirteen and that would be the case at
服务器，如果这个领导者刚刚重启，因为图两个规则
the server if this leader had just
restarted because the figure two rules
说下一个索引从新领导者日志的末尾开始，所以在
say that next index starts out at the
end of the new leaders log and so in
应对领导者应该减少其下一个误差的错误
response to errors the leaders supposed
to decrement its next in
偷，所以这样做都是因为两个人都从Boat deca先生那里得到了错误。加尔文重新发送
steal so it does that for both got
errors from boat deca mr. Calvin resends
这次服务器将发送带有前一个的追加条目
and this time the server is going to
send out append entries with previous
对数索引等于11，上一个对数项等于3，
log index equals 11
and previous log term equals 3 and this
新的追加条目具有不同的先前日志索引，但是
new append entries has it has a
different previous log index but it's
这次服务器将要发送的日志条目中的内容
the content in the log entries that the
server is going to send out this time
包括您知道之后的新先前日志索引的所有条目
include you know all the entries after
that the new previous log index is
发送出去，因此服务器2现在在其中查找先前的日志索引11，并且看到
sending out so server 2 now the previous
log index 11 it looks there and it sees
呵呵，您知道术语3与读者发送给我的术语相同，因此服务器2是
a ha you know the term is 3 same as what
the reader is sending me so server 2 is
实际上将接受此追加条目，图2规则说哦，如果您
actually going to accept this append
entries and figure 2 rules say oh if you
接受一个吊坠，我们应该删除您日志中的所有内容，
accept a pendent we supposed to delete
everything in your log after where the
追加条目开始并将其替换为追加条目中的所有内容，因此
append entry starts and replace it with
whatever's in the append entries so
服务器调整现在就可以做到
server tune is going to do that now it's
他刚去5 6服务器1仍然有问题，因为它在插槽11上什么都没有
he just went to 5 6 server 1 still has a
problem cuz it has nothing at slot 11
中间将返回另一个错误，服务器现在将备份其服务器1
middle would return another error the
server will now backup its server 1 next
index 2 11它将从上一个索引开始发送日志
index 2 11 it'll send out its log
starting here with the previous index
和术语，现在指的是该插槽和该服务器实际可接受的服务器1
and term referring now to this slot and
this one's actually acceptable server 1
它会采用它将接受新的日志条目并发送肯定的响应
it'll adopt it'll accept the new log
entries and send a positive response
回到服务器，现在他们都
back to the server and now they're all
现在他们都被赶上了
now they're all caught up and the
大概服务器也在看到跟随者接受并追加时
presumably the server also when it sees
that followers accepted and append
具有一定数量的日志条目的条目实际上会在下一个递增
entries that had a certain number of log
entries it actually increments this next
索引可能是14 4好，所以所有这些备份的最终结果是
index could be 14 4 alright so the net
effect of all this backing up is that
服务器已使用备份机制来检测
the server has used a backup mechanism
to detect the point at which the
关注者日志开始与此相等
followers logs
started to be equal to this
服务器，然后从该点开始发送每个关注者
servers and then sent each of the
followers starting from that point that
最后的那一点之后，服务器日志的完整剩余部分
a complete remainder of the server's log
after that last point at which they were
平等对待任何问题
equal any questions all right
只是要重复我们之前的讨论，我们可能会再有一个
just to repeat discussion we've had
before and we'll probably have again you
请注意，我们在此处删除了一些博客条目，这些条目现在su删除了我
notice that we erased some blog entries
here which are now su erase that I
忘了他们是4和5，所以实际上有一些很好的东西
forget what they were 4 & 5 so there
were some well actually that was mostly
记住，我们在这里删除了此日志条目，这对于um server来说是这样-
remember we erased this log entry here
this used to say for um server - the
问题是为什么系统可以忽略此客户端命令是可以的
question is why was it ok for the system
to forget about this client command
正确，我们擦除的这件事对应于现在的一些客户端命令
right this thing we erased corresponds
to some client command which are now
扔掉我昨天谈到这个是什么理由是的
throwing away I talked about this
yesterday what's the rationale here yeah
因此它不是大多数服务器，因此无论以前的领导者是什么
so it's not a majority of the servers
and therefore whatever previous leader
是谁发出来的，得到了​​大多数人的肯定
it was who sent this out couldn't have
gotten acknowledgments from a majority
的服务器，因此以前的领导者无法确定它是
of servers therefore that previous
leader couldn't have decided it was
提交的文件无法执行并将其应用于应用程序状态
committed couldn't have executed it and
applied it to the application state
永远不可能向客户发送肯定的答复，所以这不是
could never have sent a positive reply
back to the client so because this isn't
完成了大多数服务器，我们知道发送邮件的客户端没有理由
done a majority of servers we know that
the client who send in and has no reason
相信它的执行不可能得到答复，因为其中一项规则
to believe it was executed couldn't have
gotten a reply because one of the rules
是服务器仅通过领导者发送，而是仅在其之后发送答复给客户端
is the server only sends over the leader
only sends a reply to a client after it
提交并执行，因此客户没有理由相信它甚至
commits and executes so the client had
no reason to believe it was even
然后由任何服务器接收，然后根据图的规则基本上说
received by any server and then and the
rules of figure to basically say the
客户，如果他在一段时间后仍未收到任何响应，则应重新发送请求
client if he gets no response after a
while it supposed to resend the request
因此，我们知道这是什么请求，它都被抛弃了，我们从未执行过
so we know whatever request this was it
threw away we've never executed never
已包含在任何州中，客户将逐个重发
好吧，它总是删除关注者日志的后缀，我的意思是最后排序
well it's always deleting suffix of the
followers log I mean in the end the sort
后备答案的答案是，领导者拥有完整的日志，因此其所有
of backup answer to this is that the
leader has a complete log so all its
失败，它只会向我们发送完整的日志给关注者，实际上，如果您知道
fails it can just send us complete log
to the follower and indeed if you know
如果您刚刚启动了系统，即使在
if you've just started up the system and
something very strange happened even at
一开始，您可能最终会知道，也许在某些情况下
the very beginning then you may end up
actually you know maybe in some of the
测试第二个实验，您可能会备份到第一个条目，然后再备份
tests for lab two you may end up backing
up to the very first entry and then
让领导者本质上发送整个日志，但是因为领导者拥有
having the leader essentially send the
whole log but because the leader has
这整个法律，我们知道它可能会得到所有的信息
this whole law we know it could sort of
it's got all the information that's
需要感觉每个人的日志，如果需要
required to feel everybody's logs if it
needs to
好的，所以在此示例中，我想现在将其删除了，我们选择s3为
okay all right so in this example which
I guess are now erased we elected s3 as
领导者，问题是我们可以知道我们可以允许谁吗
the leader and the question is could we
you know who can we who are we allowed
选出这个领导者很酷，如果您阅读了
to elect this leader right cool
you know that all right if you read the
纸，你知道答案不只是任何人，事实证明，这对很多人都非常重要
paper you know the answer is not just
anyone it turns out it matters a lot for
正确性我们不允许任何人使用的系统的正确性
the correctness the correctness of the
system that we don't allow just anyone
成为领导者，例如计时器关闭的第一个节点可能在
to be the leader like for example the
first node whose timer goes off may in
事实上不是一个可以接受的领袖，所以事实证明筏有一些规则，
fact not be an acceptable leader and so
it turns out raft has some rules that
适用于哦，是的，您可以成为领导者，也可以不成为领导者，以了解原因
applies about oh yes you can be leader
or you can't be leader and to see why
这是真的，让我们提出一个可能是木筏的稻草人建议
this is true let's sort of set up a
straw man proposal that maybe raft
应该接受应该使用日志最长的服务器作为领导者
should accept should use the server with
the longest log as the leader right you
知道一些可能是真实的替代宇宙，实际上在
know some alternate universe that could
be true and it is actually true in
设计不同的系统只是不在筏子里，所以我们的问题是
systems with different designs just not
in raft so the question we're
调查是为什么不使用宫颈最长的法律作为领导，这
investigating is why not use the
cervical longest law as leader and this
将涉及更改筏中的投票规则，只有选民投票支持
would involve changing the voting rules
in raft have a voters only vote for
较长日志的节点可以正常运行，因此该示例将是
nodes that have longer logs all right so
the example that's going to be
方便显示为什么这是一个坏主意，让我们假设我们有三个
convenient for showing why this is a bad
idea so let's imagine we have three
再次服务器，现在日志集设置为服务器Wan，其中有条款条目
servers again and now the log set setups
are server Wan has entries for terms
五六和七服务器二四五和八，服务器三也四
five six and seven server two four five
and eight and server three also four
五和八，这是当然要避免花费时间的第一个问题
five and eight that's the first question
of course to avoid spending our time
彻底胡说八道是要确保说服
scratching our heads about utter
nonsense is to make sure that convince
我们自己认为这种配置实际上可能会出现，因为如果不能
ourselves that this configuration could
actually arise because if it couldn't
可能出现然后可能是浪费时间来弄清楚
possibly arise then
may be a waste of time to figure out
如果确实发生了会发生什么，所以任何人都想提出一系列
what would happen if it did arise so
anybody wanna propose a sequence of
可能发生这组日志的事件
events whereby this set of logs could
have arisen how about an argument that
不可能出现哦，是的，好吧，也许我们会在某个时候备份
it couldn't have arisen oh yeah okay so
well maybe we'll back up sometime
好的，这样一台服务器就赢得了胜利，这是期限
all right so server one wins is wins the
election at this point and it's in term
六个发出，是的，它收到一个客户请求，发出第一个追加
six sends out yeah it receives a client
request sends out the first append
条目，然后就可以了，实际上一切都很好，到目前为止，没有错
entries and then that's fine actually
everything's fine so far nothing's wrong
好吧，所有这些事情的好选择就是它崩溃了，否则
all right well a good bet for all these
things is then it crashes right or it
在第六学期收到客户请求，将客户请求附加到其
receives the client requests in term six
it appends the client requests to its
自己的日志，它首先会做，并且即将发送笔记录，但是它
own log which it does first and it's
about to send out a pen entries but it
崩溃是的，它没有发送任何笔输入，然后您知道我们需要
crashes yes it didn't send out any pen
entries and then you know we need then
它崩溃并很快重新启动，有一个新的选举和天哪服务器
it crashes and restarts very quickly
there's a new election and gosh server
在第七届选举中再次当选一位新领导人。
one is elected again as the as the new
leader it receives in term seven and
收到客户端请求，将其追加到其日志中，然后崩溃，然后
receives a client request appends it to
its log and then it crashes right and
然后在发生崩溃之后，我们进行了一次新的选举，也许服务器2被选举了
then after after a crashes we have a new
election maybe server 2 gets elected
这次服务器1可能现在已关闭，因此如果服务器2在
this time maybe server 1 is down now so
off the table if server 2 is elected at
在这一点上，假设服务器1仍然死了，什么是服务器，什么是服务器2
this point suppose server 1 is still
dead what term is server what server two
场地
venues
是的，八分是正确的答案，所以为什么八而不记得这个，你知道
yeah eights the right answer so why
eight and not remember this you know
现在不见了，为什么是八个而不是六个
this is now gone why eight and not six
绝对正确，因此不要写在板上，而是为了服务器一
that's absolutely right so not written
on the board but in order for server one
要在这里当选，必须获得多数节点的投票
to have been elected here it must have
votes from majority of nodes which
如果您查看投票请求，请至少包含服务器对服务器3个中的一个
include at least one of server-to-server
three if you look at the vote request
代码和图二，如果您投票赞成某人，那您应该
code and figure two if you vote for
somebody you're you're supposed to
在长期存储中记录该术语，这意味着服务器2或
record the term in persistent storage
and that means that either server 2 or
服务器3在第六学期和事实上第七学期都是新的，因此什么时候
server 3 are both new about term six and
in fact term seven and therefore when
断绝一个人，他们不能选出新的领导人，至少其中一个人知道
sever one dies and they cannot elect a
new leader at least one of them knows
如果这个词是当前词，那么当前词是8，而如果
that the current term was eight if that
one and only that one actually if
只有一个人可以赢得选举，因为它拥有
there's only one of them only that one
could win an election because it has the
他们俩都知道第八学期的末期生育率较高，如果他们都知道，对不起
higher terminal birth they both know
about term eight sorry if they both know
大约第七学期，他们俩都将成为其中的一员
about term seven then they'll both and
either one of them will try to be leader
和第八个学期，这样就可以保证下一个学期必须是疾病
and term eight so that fact of that the
next term must be term a dis is insured
由多数人的财产必须重叠和事实，当前任期
by the property of the majorities must
overlap and the fact that current term
通过投票请求进行更新，并且保持不变，并且保证没有丢失
is updated by vote request and is
persistent and guarantee did not be lost
即使这里发生了一些崩溃，所以下一学期将是八个
even if there were some crashes here so
the next term is going to be eight
服务器二或服务器三将赢得领导选举，让我们
server two or server three will win the
leadership election and let's just
想象一下，无论是哪个发送新客户端的追加条目
imagine that whichever one it is sends
out append entries for a new client
请求另一个获取它，所以现在我们有了正确的配置，因此
requests the other one gets it and so
now we have this configuration right so
我有点走弯路，我们回到了最初的问题
I was a bit of a detour we're back to
our original question of in this
配置假设服务器可以恢复运行，请选择
configuration suppose server one revives
we have an election would it be okay to
使用服务器一台，只要规则是最长的日志获胜，就可以了
use server one would it be okay to have
the rule be the longest log wins the
最长的日志成为领导者是的，显然不对，因为服务器是
longest log gets to be the leader yeah
obviously not right because server was a
领导者确实要通过附加将其登录强制给关注者
leader did it's going to force its log
on to the to followers by the append
几分钟前我们刚刚谈到的条目机制
entries machinery that we just talked
about a few minutes ago
如果我们将服务器作为领导者，那您就会知道发出了一支钢笔
if we live server one to be the leader
it's gonna you know sent out a pen
条目（无论备份如何覆盖）都会帮助追随者擦除其内容
entries whatever backup overwrite these
aids tell the followers to erase their
术语a的日志条目接受用这六个和七个覆盖它们
log entries for term a to accept to
overwrite them with this six and seven
日志条目，然后继续与服务器相同，因此当然
log entries and then to proceed now with
identical to server ones so of course
为什么我们对此感到不安呢？
why are we upset about this yeah yeah
exactly it was already committed right
不是大多数服务器已经执行了提交
it's not a majority of servers has
already committed probably executed
很可能发送给客户的回复，因此我们无权删除它，并且
quite possibly a reply sent to a client
so we're not entitled to delete it and
因此，不能允许服务器一成为领导者并强制其登录
therefore server one cannot be allowed
to become leader and force its log onto
服务器2和3每个人都知道为什么这对于快速来说是个坏主意，并且因为
servers two and three everybody see why
that's bad idea for rapid and because of
当然这不可能是最短日志选举的规则
that this can't possibly have been rule
for elections of course shortest log
也不是很好，所以事实上，如果您继续阅读本节
didn't work too well either and so in
fact if you read forward to section
五点四点一
something five point four point one
草案实际上具有稍微复杂的选举限制，
draft actually has a slightly more
sophisticated election restriction that
请求投票处理RPC处理代码应该在它说之前进行检查
the request vote handling RPC handling
code is supposed to check before it says
是，先投票，是其他同伴，规则是我们只投票给您
yes before votes yes for a different
peer and the rule is we only vote you
对某些候选人发送赞成票，仅在候选人具有
vote yes for some candidate who send us
over request votes only if candidate has
更高的
a higher
上一个日志条目中的术语或相同的上一个术语相同的迷人的上一个日志条目
term in the last log entry or same last
term same charming the last log entry
并且日志长度大于或等于接收到的服务器
and a log length that's greater than or
equal to the the server that received
接收到船的请求，因此如果服务器二获得一个请求，我们在这里应用
that received the boat request and so if
we apply this here if server two gets a
来自服务器的表决请求之一是我们最后的日志输入条款，或者是七个服务器
vote request from server one there our
last log entry terms or seven the server
一个人要发出一个投票请求，最后一个入学期限为7
one's gonna send out a request votes
with a last entry term whatever of 7
服务器二是八，所以这不是真正的服务器服务，我们没有收到请求
server twos is eight so this isn't true
server service we didn't get a request
在最后一项或最后一项中具有较高任期的人
from somebody with a higher term in the
last entry and or the last entry terms
也不一样，第二个条款也不适用，所以
aren't the same either said the second
Clause doesn't apply either so neither
服务器到新服务或服务器三将投票给服务器一，所以甚至
server to new serve nor server three is
going to vote for server one and so even
如果它首先发出此投票请求，因为它的选举时间较短
if it sends out this vote requests first
because this has a shorter election
超时，除了它本身，没人会投票支持，所以我认为这不是一个
timeout nobody's going to vote for it
except itself so I don't think it's one
如果第二台服务器或第三台服务器成为一个服务器，则投票不是多数
vote it's not a majority if either
server two or server three becomes a
候选人，那么他们中的任何一个都会接受另一个，因为他们拥有
candidate then either of them will
accept the other because they have the
上一个学期的数字相同，并且其日志的长度均大于或等于
same last term number and their logs are
each greater than or equal to in length
和其他人，因此他们中的任何一个都将投票给另一个，这将是服务器
and the others so either of them will
vote for for the other one will server
对其中任何一个投一票，是因为服务器2或服务器3
one vote for either of them
yes because either server 2 or server 3
在最后一个条目中有较高的学期号，所以您知道这是在做什么
has a higher term number in the last
entry so you know what this is doing is
确保只有在或喜欢候选人时您才能成为候选人
making sure that you can only become a
candidate if or it prefers candidates
知道更高的具有日志条目的一些更高的术语
that knew about higher that have log
entries some higher terms that is it
倾向于更可能从接收日志条目的候选人
prefers candidates that are more likely
to have been receiving log entries from
前任领导人，您知道第二部分说的很好，我们都是
the previous leader and you know this
second part says well we were all
听前一个领导，然后我们将
listening to the previous leader then
we're going to
对于从最后一位领导者那里看到更多请求的服务器
for the server that has saw more
requests from the very last leader any
有关选举限制的问题
questions about the election restriction
关于发送日志条目的最后一件事是，该回滚方案位于
okay final thing about sending out log
entries is that this rollback scheme at
至少正如我描述的那样，如图2所示，它回滚了一个
least as I described it and it's as its
described in Figure two rolls back one
一次登录日志，您可能会发现很多有趣的事
log entry at a time and you know
probably a lot of fun that's okay
但是有些情况可能在现实世界中而且肯定在实验室中
but there are situations maybe in the
real world and definitely in the lab
测试一次备份一个条目将花费很长时间的测试
tests where backing up one entry at a
time is going to take a long long time
因此，在现实世界中，如果
and so the real-world situation where
that might be true is if they if a
追随者已经失望了很长一段时间，错过了很多高端作品，
follower has been down for a long time
and missed a lot of upend entries and
领导者重新启动，如果您遵循图2中的伪代码，
the leader restarts and if you follow
the pseudocode in Figure two if a leader
重新启动应该将其下一个索引设置为Leader日志的末尾，因此
restarts is supposed to set its next
index to the end of the leaders log so
如果关注者已关闭并且您知道错过了最后一千条日志
if the follower has been down and you
know miss the last thousand log entries
领导重新启动领导将不得不一次退后一步
and leader reboots the leader is gonna
have to walk back off one at a time one
一次跟随RPC追随者错过的所有数千个日志条目，
RPC at a time all thousand of those log
entries that the follower missed and
您不知道为什么这在现实生活中永远不会发生的特定原因
there's no you know particular reason
why this would never happen in real life
在某些人为的情况下很容易发生测试
it could easily happen at somewhat more
contrived situation that the tests are
如果我们说我们有五台服务器，
definitely explorers is if a follower is
if we say we have five servers and
有一个领导者，但是领导者被一个追随者困在一个
there's there's a leader but the leaders
got trapped with one follower in a
网络分区，但领导者不知道它不再是领导者，而是
network partition but the leader doesn't
know it's not leader anymore and it's
仍然向其一个关注者发送附加条目，但没有一个是
still sending out append entries to its
one follower and none of which are
在另一个多数分区中提交时，系统将继续
committed while in the other majority
partition the system is continuing as
通常情况下，该少数民族分区的前领导人和追随者可能最终把
usual the ex leader and follower in that
Minority partition could end up putting
在他们的日志中，您知道某种陈旧术语的日志条目数量不受限制
in their logs you know sort of unlimited
numbers of log entries for a stale term
永远不会提交，最终需要删除和覆盖
that will never be committed and need to
be deleted and overwritten eventually
当他们重新加入主要群体时，在现实中的可能性可能会降低一些
when they rejoin the main group that's
maybe a little less likely in the real
世界，但您会看到它的发生并进行了测试，以便能够
world but you'll see it happen and the
test set up so in order to be able to
备份得更快，该论文对更快的描述有些含糊
back up faster that paper has
somewhat a vague description of a faster
5.3节末尾的方案，这有点难以解释，因此
scheme towards the end of section 5.3
it's a little bit hard to interpret so
我将尝试解释他们关于如何更快备份的想法
I'm gonna try to explain what their
ideas about how to back up faster a
好一点了，一般的想法是能够拥有跟随者
little bit better and the general idea
is to be able to to have the follower
向领导发送足够的信息，使领导可以跳回整个
send enough information to the leader
that the leader can jump back an entire
每个附加条目都必须删除的条目的术语价值，以使其领先
terms worth of entries that have to be
deleted per append entries so it leader
可能只需要发送一个三角旗并在每个学期附加条目，其中
may only have to send one in a pennant
and append entries per term in which the
领导者和跟随者不同意，而不是每个条目一个，所以我有三种情况
leader and follower disagree instead of
one per entry so there's three cases I
认为很重要，事实是您可能会想到许多不同的事物
think are important and the fact is that
you can probably think of many different
日志备份加速策略，这是一个，所以我将划分
log backup acceleration strategies and
here's one so I'm going to divide the
您可能会看到三种情况，这是快速备份情况
kinds of situations you might see into
three cases so this is fast backup case
我只想谈论一位追随者和领导者，不用担心
one I'm just going to talk about one
follower and the leader and not worry
关于其他节点相同，我们有两个服务器，一个是跟随者，另一个是
about the other nodes the same we have
two server one which is the follower and
服务器2是领导者，所以这是一种情况，在这里我们需要备份
server 2 which is the leader so this is
one case and here we need to backup over
领导者完全缺少该术语的另一种情况
a term where that term is entirely
missing from the leader another case
因此，在这种情况下，我们需要备份一些条目，但是它们的条目
so in this case we need to back up over
some entries but their entries for a
领导者实际上很了解这个词的人
term that the leader actually knows
about so apparently the this followers
看到了几个条目，几个非常少的附加条目已发送出去
saw a couple of entry a couple of the
very Flass few append entries sent out
一个即将坠毁的领导者，但新的领导者没有看到他们，我们仍然
by a leader that was about to crash but
the new leader didn't see them we still
需要备份他们，第三种情况是追随者完全
need to back up over them and a third
case is where the followers entirely
缺少以下领导者同意，但追随者却错过了结尾
missing the following the leader agree
but the followers is missing the end of
领导者的日志，我相信您可以通过
the leaders log and I believe you can
take care of all three of these with
追随者发送回给他们的回复中的三段额外信息
three pieces of extra information in the
reply that a follower sends back to the
追加条目中案例的领导者，所以我们在谈论追加
leader in the case in the append entries
so we're talking about the append
如果追随者拒绝附加条目，则条目会回复，因为日志
entries reply if the follower rejects
the append entries because the logs
不同意以下三点信息，
don't agree there's three pieces of
information that will be useful and
照顾三个街头案例，我称它们为X词，即
taking care of three street cases I'll
call them X term which is the term of
我记得领导者发送了这个先前的日志术语，这是有冲突的条目，
the conflicting entry I remember the
leader sent this previous log term and
如果追随者拒绝它，因为它在这里有东西，但术语错误
if the follower rejects it because it
has something here but the terms wrong
这样就可以在这里将关注者词条用于冲突条目，否则您就知道我是
so it'll put the followers term for the
conflicting entry here or you know I'm
负数或某事它在日志中没有任何内容
negative one or something it doesn't
have anything in the log there it'll
还发回有冲突的索引，但索引是第一个
also send back the index of the
conflicting but the index are the first
该词项
entry with that term
最后，如果根本没有任何日志条目，那么关注者将
and finally if there wasn't any log
entry there at all the follower will
像追随者日志一样发送其法律的长度，因此对于情况一
send back on the length of its law like
the followers log so for case one the
如果领导者看到领导者甚至没有
way this helps if the it's a leader sees
that the leader doesn't even have an
在其日志中根本没有X项的X项的条目，因此在这种情况下
entry with X term of term X term at all
in its log so that's this case where the
领导者没有五号位，如果领导者可以简单地回到
leader didn't have turn five and if the
leader can simply back up to the
跟随者的开头是X项，即
beginning of the followers run of
entries with X term that is the the
领导者可以将其下一个索引设置为此X索引对象，这是
leader can set its next index to this X
index thing which is the first entry the
跟随者运行第五学期的项目，所以如果领导者没有X
followers run of items from term five
alright so if the leader doesn't have X
术语，它应该备份到X，将跟随者备份到X，第二个索引
term at all it should back up to X back
the follower up to X index the second
如果您可以检测到故障，领导者可以检测X项是否有效，并且
case you can detect the fault the leader
can detect if X term is valid and the
领导者实际上有项X项的日志条目，在这种情况下，
leader actually has log entries of term
X term that's the case here where the
你知道分歧在这里，但领导者实际上有一些条目
you know the disagreement is here but
the leader actually has some entries
在这种情况下，领导者应备份到其具有的最后一个条目
that term in that case the leader should
back up to the last entry it has that
最后一个有冲突的字词的竞赛者追随者，这是最后一个
has the contesta followers term for the
conflicting term in it that is the last
在这种情况下，如果两个都不是领导者所要担任的职位
entry that a leader has for term for in
this case and if neither of these two
如果追随者通过可能的设置表明情况，那么案例实际上就是好的
cases hold that is the well actually if
the follower indicates by maybe setting
X项减一，实际上它什么也没有
X term to minus one it actually didn't
have anything whatsoever at the
日志和索引冲突，因为日志太短，那么领导者应该
conflicting log and index because it's
log is too short then the leader should
将其下一个索引备份到关注者根本拥有的最后一个条目，然后开始
back up its next index to the last entry
that the follower had at all and start
从那里发送，我告诉你这是因为
sending from there
and I'm telling you this because it'll
对进行实验很有用，如果您错过了我的一些描述，那是在
be useful for doing a lab and if you
miss some of my description it's it's in
电子，那么关于这个备份业务的任何问题我想杰克
electronics then any questions about
this backing up business Jack I think
是的，是的，是的，也许是二进制搜索，但我不排除其他
that's true yeah yeah yeah maybe binary
search I'm not ruling out other
解决方案，我的意思是，您在阅读论文的非说明后就知道了
solutions I mean that you know after
reading the papers non description of
怎么做我喜欢做这个，可能还有其他方法
how to do it I like cook this up and
there's probably other ways to do this
大概是更好的方法和更快的方法，就像我确定
probably better ways and faster ways of
doing it like I'm I'm sure that if
您愿意发回更多信息或获得更复杂的信息
you're willing to send back more
information or have a more sophisticated
像二进制搜索这样的策略，您可以做得更好，是的，您几乎
strategy like binary search you can do a
better job yeah well you you almost
当然需要做一些经验表明，为了
certainly need to do something
experience suggests that in order to
通过测试，您可能需要对我做一些事情
pass the tests you'll need to do
something to as well probably not me
尽管我不像我写过的一种解决方案那样完全正确
although I that's not quite true like
one of the solutions I've written over
岁月实际上做了愚蠢的事情，仍然通过了测试，但是因为
the years actually does the stupid thing
and still passes the tests but because
您知道的测试是一种不幸但不可避免的事情
the tests you know the one of the sort
of unfortunate but inevitable things
关于我们提供给您的测试，他们对实时性有一些要求
about the tests we give you is that they
have a bit of a real time requirement
那就是测试不愿永远等待您的解决方案
that is the tests are not willing to
wait forever for your solution to
给出答案，这样就有可能找到您所知道的解决方案
produce an answer so it is possible to
have a solution that's you know
从技术上讲是正确的，但要花很长时间，以至于测试人员放弃
technically correct but takes so long
that the tester gives up and
不幸的是，您知道如果您的解决方案，测试人员将使您失败
unfortunately you know we will the
tester will fail you if your solution
没有完成测试，无论时限如何，因此您可以
doesn't finish the test and whatever the
time limit is and therefore you do
实际上必须要注意性能，以便您了解自己的
actually have to pay some attention to
performance in order you know your
解决方案必须既正确又要有足够的性能才能完成
solution has to be both correct and have
enough performance to finish before the
测试员很无聊，有时会在你身上出来，大概是10分钟，否则我不会
tester gets bored and sometimes out on
you which is like 10 minutes or I don't
知道它是什么，不幸的是，相对来说这东西足够复杂
know what it is and unfortunately it's
relatively this stuff's complex enough
写色彩校正并不难
that it's not that hard to write a color
correction
这不够快，是的，所以您可以利用领导者的方式告诉
that's not fast enough yes so the way
you can tap the leader can tell the
区别在于我们应该向跟随者发送术语号
difference is that the follower we're
supposed to send back the term number it
看到在冲突的条目中，如果领导者没有
sees in the conflicting entry you we
have case one if the leader does not
在其日志中包含该术语，因此在此关注者会将X术语设置为
have that term in its log
so here the follower will set X term to
五到五，因为这将是这将是
five to five because this is this is
going to be the this is gonna be the
冲突的词条追随者对领导者说的这个X术语表示五个
conflicting entry the follower says this
X term to five the leader observes oh I
在我的日志中没有第五学期，因此这种情况一，你知道
do not have term five in my log and
therefore this case one and you know it
应该备份到开始，就像没有跟随者没有领导者一样
should back up to the beginning
like it doesn't follower hasn't leader
没有任何一个，而第五学期进入，所以它应该摆脱所有这些
has none of those and term five entry so
it should just get rid of all of them in
通过备份到X索引的开头来跟随者
the follower by backing up to the
beginning which is X index yeah yeah
因为领导者会将其下一个索引备份到此处，然后发送
because the leaders gonna back up its
next index to here and then send an
追加从此处开始的条目，然后规则一个数字说“追随者”
append entries that starts here and the
rules a figure to say ah the follower
只需替换它的日志，这样就可以摆脱击掌了，好吧
just has to replace its log so it is
gonna get rid of the fives okay alright
接下来要谈的是持久性，您将在图二中注意到
the next thing I want to talk about is
persistence you'll notice in Figure two
左上角的状态分为夏季和夏季
that the state in the upper left-hand
corners sort of divided and summer
标记为持久性，某些标记为易失性，这里发生的是
marked persistent and some are marked
volatile and what's going on here is
持久性和易失性之间的区别只知道
that the the distinction between
persistence and volatile you know only
服务器重新启动崩溃和重新启动很重要，因为持久性
matters if a server reboots crashes and
restarts because the persistent what the
持久的意思是，如果您更改其中一项，则将其标记为
persistent means is that if you change
one of those items it's marked
持久性，您应该将其写入服务器或磁盘中
persistent you're supposed to the server
supposed to write it to disk or to some
其他非易失性存储，例如as或电池支持的东西
other non-volatile storage like as
or battery-backed something or whatever
这将确保如果服务器重新启动，它将能够找到
that will ensure that if the server
restarts that it will be able to find
这些信息并将其重新加载到内存中，这使我们能够
that information and sort of reload it
into memory and that's to allow us to
允许服务器在发生崩溃时能够从中断处继续取回，
allow servers to be able to pick up
where they left off if they crash and
现在重新启动，您可能会认为它会足够并且更简单
restart now you might think that it
would it would be sufficient and simpler
说得好，如果服务器崩溃，那么我们就把它扔掉，或者我们需要
to say well if a server crashes then we
just throw it away and or we need to be
能够将其丢弃并替换为全新的空服务器并带来
able to throw it away and replace it
with a brand-new empty server and bring
使其达到正确的速度，当然，您实际上要做的是能够做到
it up to speed right and of course you
do actually it is vital to be able to do
没错，因为如果某个服务器遭受了灾难性的故障
that right because if some server
suffers a failure of some catastrophic
像失败一样，您知道磁盘融化或您绝对需要的某些功能
failure like it's you know disk melts or
something you absolutely need to be able
替换它，您不能指望从其磁盘上获得任何有用的东西，如果
to replace it and you cannot count on
getting anything useful off its disk if
磁盘发生了问题，因此我们绝对需要能够更换
something bad happened to its disk so we
absolutely need to be able to replace
完全替换无状态的服务器，您可能会认为这是
completely replace servers that have no
state whatsoever you might think that's
足以应付任何困难，但事实并非如此
sufficient to handle any difficulties
but it's actually not it turns out that
另一个常见的故障模式是您知道整个群集的电源故障
another common failure mode is power
failure of you know the entire cluster
他们都在同一时间停止执行，在这种情况下，我们
where they all stop executing at the
same time right and in that case we
无法解决或者我们无法通过简单地扔掉
can't handle or we can't handle that
failure by simply throwing away the
服务器，并用我们从戴尔购买的新硬件替换它们
servers and replacing them with new
hardware that we buy from Dell we
实际上必须能够起步，我们需要能够获得副本
actually have to be able to get off the
ground we need to be able to get a copy
返回状态以保持执行，如果我们希望我们的服务
of the state back in order to keep
executing if we want our service to be
容错的，因此至少是为了处理这种情况
fault tolerant and therefore in order at
least in order to handle the situation
同时发生电源故障，我们必须有一种方法使服务器能够
of simultaneous power failure we have to
have a way for the server's to sort of
将其状态保存在电源恢复供电的位置
save their state somewhere where it will
be available when the power returns and
这是观察持久性情况的一种方式，它说
that's one way of viewing what's going
on with persistence it said that's the
要求重新启动服务器所需的状态
state that's required
to get a server going again I'm after
单个电源故障或整个集群的电源故障
either a single power failure or power
failure of the entire cluster
好吧，图二这三个项目只有三个项目是持久的，所以
alright so figure two this three items
only three items are persistent so
有一个类似于当前所有日志条目并被投票支持的日志
there's a log that's like all the log
entries current term and voted for and
通过您知道我们其中一台服务器重新启动的方式，它实际上必须进行
by the way you know one of us server
reboots it actually has to make an
显式检查以确保这些数据在其磁盘上有效
explicit check to make sure that these
data are valid on its disk before it
重新加入木筏群，我必须要说些什么哦，是的，我实际上是
rejoins the raft cluster I have to have
some way of saying oh yeah I actually do
有一些保存持久状态，而不是一堆零
have some save persistent state as
opposed to a bunch of zeros that that
是无效的，所以必须保留日志的原因是
are not valid all right so the reason
why log has to be persisted is that at
至少根据图二，这是应用程序状态的唯一记录
least according to figure two this is
the only record of the application state
那是图二并没有真正的概念，害怕二没有说我们
that is figure two doesn't really have a
notion fears two does not say that we
必须保持应用程序状态，以便我们运行数据库还是您知道
have to persist the application state so
if we're running a database or you know
测试和设置服务，例如针对vmware的实际数据库或实际
a test and set service like for vmware
ft the actual database or the actual
仅根据图二，test and set标志的值不是持久的
value of the test and set flag isn't
persistent according to figure two only
登录名，因此当服务器重新启动时，只有可用的信息
the logins and so when the server
restarts the only information available
重建应用程序状态是日志中的命令序列，
to reconstruct the application state is
the sequence of commands in the log and
因此必须坚持下去，这就是当前术语的原因
so that has to be persisted that's what
about current term why does current term
必须坚持
have to be persistent
是的，所以他们俩都在确保每个学期只有一个
yeah so they're both about ensuring that
there's only one that each term has at
最多一位领导人，所以是的，所以投票赞成具体的内容，您知道这可能会造成破坏
most one leader so yeah so voted for the
specific you know potential damaging
情况是，如果服务器收到船请求并投票给服务器一，
case is that if a server receives a boat
request and votes for server one and
然后崩溃，如果不坚持下去，谁投票的身份
then it crashes and if it didn't persist
this the identity of who had voted for
在坠机事故中，我们开始从
and in my crash we start get another
boat request for the same term from
服务器二，说天哪，我没有投票给任何人，因为我的投票是
server two and say gosh I haven't voted
for anybody because my voted for is
我现在要为服务器2投票
blank
now I'm gonna vote for server 2 and now
我们的服务器在同一期限内对服务器1和服务器2进行了投票，这可能
our servers voted for server 1 and for
server 2 in the same term and that might
允许两台服务器，因为服务器和服务器均已投票
allow two servers
since both server and server to voted
他们俩可能都认为自己拥有三分之二的多数，
for themselves they both may think they
have a majority out of three and they're
两者都将成为领导者现在我们有两个同时的服务器用于同一个
both going to become leader now we have
two simultaneous servers for the same
这个词，所以这就是为什么我投票赞成必须持续使用当前词是
term so this that's why I voted for it
has to be persistent current term is
会更加微妙，但实际上我们之前谈到过
gonna be a little more subtle but we
actually talked before about how you
再次知道我们不希望一个学期拥有多个服务器，如果我们
know again we don't want to have more
than one server for a term and if we
不知道这是什么术语号，那么我们就不一定那么难了
don't know what term number it is then
we can't necessarily then it may be hard
确保一个学期只有一台服务器，我想也许
to ensure that there's only one server
for a term and I think maybe in this
例如，如果服务器1宕机，服务器2和服务器3宕机，我们将尝试
example ya if s if server 1 was down and
server 2 and server 3 we're gonna try to
选择一台新服务器，他们需要证明正确的转弯数字是8，而不是
elect a new server they need evidence
that the correct turn numbers 8 and not
6对，因为如果他们忘记了当前任期，那仅仅是
6 right because if they if they forgot
about current term and it was just
服务器2和服务器3互相投票，并且他们只有日志
server 2 and server 3 voting for each
other and they only had their log to
看看他们可能认为下一学期应该是第六学期
look at they might think the next term
should be term 6 they did that they
开始为第六学期生产东西，但是现在会有很多困惑
start producing stuff for term 6 but now
there's gonna be a lot of confusion
因为我们有两个不同的学期六，所以这就是我当前学期的原因
because we have two different term sixes
and so that's the reason my current term
必须坚持不懈地保存有关具有
has to be persistent to preserve
evidence about term numbers that have
已经被使用过，每次您都必须坚持使用这些
already been used these have to be
persisted pretty much every time you
正确地更改它们，所以安全的做法当然是每次添加
change them right so certainly the safe
thing to do is every time you add an
记录日志或更改当前词条表示已投票赞成您可能需要您
entry of log or change current term
are said voted for you need you probably
需要坚持下去，并在一个真正的木筏服务器上，这意味着将其写入
need to persist that and in a real raft
server that would mean writing it to the
磁盘，以便您有一些文件记录了这些东西，您可以
disk so you'd have some set of files
that recorded this stuff you can
如果观察到一点，您可能会偷偷摸摸
probably be a little bit you may be can
cut some corners if you observed that
在与外界沟通之前，您不需要坚持这些事情
you don't need to persist these things
until you communicate with the outside
因此，可能会有一些进行批量处理的机会，方法是说
world so there may be some opportunity
for a little bit of batching by saying
好吧，在我们要回复RPC或
well we don't have to persist anything
until we're about to reply to an RPC or
即将发出RPC，我的意思是可以避免出现一些持续存在的x'
about to send out an RPC I mean that may
allow you to avoid a few persisting x'
重要的原因是将内容写入磁盘可能非常
the reason that's important is that
writing stuff to disk is can be very
昂贵的话，那是我们要谈论的机械硬盘
expensive it's a if it's a mechanical
hard drive that we're talking about then
如果我们坚持的方式是在
writing anything you know if the way
we're persisting is writing files on the
磁盘在磁盘上写入任何内容都会花费大约10毫秒，因为
disk writing anything on the disk cost
you about 10 milliseconds because you
要么等待磁盘旋转到要写入的点
either have to wait for the disk to spin
for the point you want to write to spin
在磁头下方，磁盘仅每10毫秒旋转一次，或者
under the head which disk only rotates
about once every 10 milliseconds or
更糟糕的是，您可能实际上不得不设法将手臂向正确的方向移动，因此
worse that you may actually have to seek
to move the arm the right track right so
这些每个系统可能非常昂贵，如果要
these per systems can be terribly
terribly expensive and if for sort of
任何一种简单的设计都可能成为限制因素
any kind of straightforward design
they're likely to be the limiting factor
表现，因为它们意味着可以做任何事情
in performance because they mean that
doing anything anything whatsoever on
这些图形服务器需要10毫秒的弹出时间和10毫秒的时间
these graph servers takes ten
milliseconds a pop and 10 milliseconds
比说发送RPC或几乎其他任何内容所需的时间长
as far longer than it takes to say send
an RPC or almost anything else you might
每次执行10毫秒意味着将数据持久存储到
do 10 milliseconds each means you can
just never if you persist data to a
机械驱动器，您永远无法建立筏服务，它可以提供更多服务
mechanical drive you just can never
build a raft service it can serve more
每秒超过100个请求，因为这就是您在10时获得的请求
than 100 requests per second because
that's what you get it at 10
每次操作的毫秒数，您知道这是成本，所以这实际上就是全部
milliseconds per operation and you know
this is this cost so this is really all
关于同步成本
about cost of synchronous
只是更新，它出现在许多系统中，例如文件系统
just updates and it comes up in many
systems like file systems the file
您的笔记本电脑上运行的系统是设计人员花费大量资金的
systems that are running in your laptops
are that the designers spend a huge
试图解决性能问题的时间量
amount of time sort of trying to
navigate around the performance problems
他们将同步磁盘的数量视为磁盘写入，因为为了进行填充
of synchronous disk up they think of as
disk writes because in order for stuff
确保磁盘安全，以便更新笔记本电脑上的文件系统
to get safe on your disk in order to
update the file system on your laptop's
安全地找到磁盘，结果文件系统必须喜欢如何
disk safely there turns out the file
system has to like be careful about how
它会写入，有时需要等待磁盘完成写入，因此这
it writes and needs to sometimes wait
for the disk to finish writing so this
就像跨系统的问题，肯定会出现在所有系统中
is a like a cross-cutting issue in all
kinds of systems certainly comes up in
草案，如果您要构建一个系统，则可以提供一百多个
draft if you want it to build a system
they could serve more than a hundred
每秒的任务数，那么会有很多选择，一个是您可以使用
quests per second then there's a bunch
of options one is you can use a
固态驱动器或某种闪存或固态八驱动器可以完成的任务
solid-state drive or some kind of flash
or something solid eight drives can do a
可能需要十分之一毫秒的时间写入闪存
write to the flash memory in maybe a
tenth of a millisecond so that's a
系数为您的一百倍，或者如果您更加精明，也许您可​​以
factor of a hundred for you or if you're
even more sophisticated maybe you can
建立自己的电池供电DRAM，并在电池供电方面保持持久性
build yourself battery backed DRAM and
do the persistence into battery back
DRAM，然后如果服务器重新启动，则希望重新启动的时间比重新启动的时间短
DRAM and then if the server reboots hope
that reboot was took shorter than the
电池可持续使用的时间量，并且您持续存在的电量仍然
amount of time the battery lasts and
that this stuff you persisted is still
在内存中的原因，我的意思是，如果您有钱又精明的原因
in the RAM and the reason I mean if you
have money and sophistication the reason
赞成您可以每秒写入数百万次的DRAM，因此
to favor that is you can write DRAM you
know millions of times per second and so
无论如何这可能不会成为性能瓶颈，
it's probably not going to be a
performance bottleneck anyway so that
这个问题是为什么，它在某种程度上标记了持久性与易变性，
this problem is why and it's sort of
marking a persistent versus volatile and
图2对性能以及
figure 2 is like has a lot of
significance for performance as well as
崩溃恢复和正确性有关持续存在的任何问题
crash recovery and correctness any
questions about persisting yeah
是的，所以您的问题基本上是您在编写代码，说去
yes alright so your question is
basically you're writing code say go
筏实现的代码，或者您试图编写一个真正的r子手
code for your raft implementation or
you're trying to write a real rafterman
实施，您实际上要确保当您坚持
implementation and you actually want to
make sure that when you persist your an
更新法律或当前条款或实际上存在的任何条款
update to the law or the current term or
whatever that it in fact will be there
崩溃后重新启动，就像您要做的食谱是什么
after a crash and reboot like what's the
recipe for what you have to do to make
确保它在那里，并且您观察到，如果您在UNIX或
sure it's there and your observation
that if you call you know on a UNIX or
Linux或任何Mac（如果您调用正确）都知道正确的系统调用是
Linux or whatever Mac if you call right
you know the right system call is how
您将其写入磁盘文件时，只需指出就可以了。
you write to a disk file you simply call
right as you pointed out it is not the
在写入返回后，数据在磁盘上是安全的，并且在
case that after the write returns the
data is safe on disk and will survive a
重新启动它几乎可以肯定不是几乎不在磁盘上，所以您知道
reboot it almost certainly isn't almost
certainly not on disk so the you know
您需要以所需的任何速率在UNIX上进行特定的魔术操作
the particular piece of magic you need
to do is on unix at any rate you need
您需要调用正确的权限，以便您无法写一些打开的文件
you need to call right so you cannot
write some file you've opened that's
将包含您要编写的内容，然后您调用了这个F
going to contain the stuff that you want
to write and then you got a call this F
圣呼叫在大多数系统上保证F同步不返回
st. call which on most systems the
guarantee is that F sync doesn't return
直到您之前写入此文件的所有数据安全地放在
until all the data you've previously
written into this file is safely on the
如果介质仍然存在，则将其放在介质上
surface on the media in a place on a
place where it will still be there if
发生了车祸，所以这件事是一些东西，然后这个电话是一个昂贵的电话，
there's a crash so so this thing is some
then this call is an expensive call and
这就是为什么它是单独的，这就是为什么Wright不只写磁盘F的原因
that's why it's a separate that's why
Wright doesn't write the disk only F
同步确实是因为它是如此昂贵，除非您不愿意这样做
sync does is because it's so expensive
you would never want to do it unless you
真的想保留一些数据，以便可以使用更昂贵的数据
really wanted to persist some stuff some
data okay so you can use more expensive
磁盘硬件人们经常使用的另一个技巧是尝试批量处理
disk hardware the other trick people
play a lot is to try to batch that is if
如果客户请求很多，您可以输入
you can if client requests are if you
have a lot of client requests coming in
也许您应该接受其中的许多内容，而不要对其中的任何内容进行回复
maybe you should accept a lot of them
and not reply to any of them for a
一点点，我们称之为很多
little bit we call a lot of them
accumulate
然后坚持下去，您一次可以从一百个日志条目中了解一百个日志条目
and then persist you know a hundred log
entries at a time from your hundred
客户并且您只知道然后发送附加条目就好了，因为您这样做
clients and you know only then send out
the append entries good because you do
如果您收到客户端请求，实际上必须将这些东西持久保存到磁盘
actually have to persist this stuff to
disk if you receive a client request you
您必须先将新条目持久化到磁盘，然后再发送附加条目
have to persist the new entry to disk
before you send the append entries our
PC追随者，因为如果认识的领导者不允许
PCs the followers because you're not
allowed if the leader you know the
领导者，基本上是承诺提交该请求，并且不能
leader it's essentially promising to
commit that that request and can't
忘记它，确实追随者必须坚持
forget about it
and indeed the followers have to persist
在他们回复附加条目之前，将新的日志条目添加到其磁盘，因为
the new log entry to their disk before
they reply to the append entries because
它们被应用于追加条目，这也是保留和保证的承诺。
they were apply to the append entries
it's also a promise to preserve and
最终提交该日志条目，以便在以下情况下不能忘记它们：
eventually commit that log entry so they
can't be allowed to forget about it if
他们最终会碰到其他有关持久性的问题
they crash other questions about
persistence all right well final you
知道关于持久性的一些细节是，图二中的一些内容
know a little detail about persistence
is that some of the stuff in figure two
不是持久的，所以值得为之挠头
is not persistent and so it's worth
scratching your head a little bit about
为什么提交索引会持续应用下一个索引并匹配索引，为什么它是公平的游戏
why commit index lasts apply next index
and match index why it's fair game for
如果服务器崩溃并重新启动，则只需将它们丢弃，就像为什么
them to be simply thrown away if the
server crashes and restarts like why
您不是不是知道提交索引还是最后一次应用它，就像geez最后一次应用是
wasn't you know commit index or last
apply it like geez last applied is the
记录如果我们扔掉了，我们执行了多少，不是吗
record of how much we've executed right
if we throw that away aren't we gonna
两次执行日志条目，这是正确的，为什么呢？为什么呢？
execute log entries twice and is that
correct how about that why is why is it
安全丢弃最后应用
safe to throw away last applied
是的，我是所有人，这里都是筏子的简单性和安全性，所以这就是
yes I am we're all about simplicity and
safety here with raft so that's exactly
纠正为什么所有其他内容都随您变化的原因
correct the the reason why all that
other stuff can be non-volatile as you
提到我的意思是对不起多变，为什么其他领域可以
mentioned I mean sorry volatile the
reason why those other fields can be
易变而被抛弃的是，我们可以使领导者重建
volatile and thrown away is that we can
the leader can reconstruct sort of
通过检查自己的日志和附加结果提交的内容
what's been committed by inspecting its
own log and by the results of append
发送给关注者的条目，最初是指领导者，如果
entries that it sends out to the
followers I mean initially the leader if
如果每个人都因为停电而重新启动
it if everybody restarts because they
experienced a power failure
最初，领导者不知道承诺了什么，执行了什么，但是
initially the leader does not know
what's committed what's executed but
当它发出日志并追加条目时，它将收集一些信息
when it sends out log and append entries
it'll sort of gather back information
基本上是追随者关于他们的日志中有多少匹配
and essentially from the followers about
What's in how much of their logs match
领导者，因此在坠机前必须付出多少
the leaders and therefore how much must
have been committed before the crash
4-2世界中的另一件事不是真实世界
another thing in the 4-2 world which is
not the real world
关于图2的另一件事是，图2假定应用程序
another thing about figure two is that
figure two assumes that the application
如果重新启动时发生崩溃，则状态会被破坏并丢弃，因此
state is destroyed and thrown away if
there's a crash in a restart so the
图二世界假设，当日志持续存在时，应用程序状态
figure two world assumes that while log
is persistent that the application state
绝对不是持久性的，要求与图2不一致，因为
is absolutely not persistent required
not to be consistent in figure 2 because
在图2中，日志从一开始就保存下来
the in figure 2 the log is preserved
persisted from the very beginning of the
系统，那么如果您播放各种内容，将会发生什么
system and so what's going to happen if
you sort of play out what the various
领导重新启动后，图2中的规则是领导最终将重新
rules in figure 2 after a leader restart
is that the leader will eventually re
执行传递给您知道的应用程序的每个日志条目
execute every single log entry that is
handed to the application you know
从重新启动后的日志条目一开始，木筏将交给
starting with log entry one after a
reboot it's the raft is gonna hand the
应用程序，每个日志条目都从一个开始，这样一来
application every log entry starting
from one and so that will after a
重新启动应用程序将完全从头开始重建其状态。
restart the application will completely
reconstruct its state from scratch by a
每次重新启动后，从整个日志的时间开始重播；
replay from the beginning of the time of
the entire log after each restart and
再次，这就像是一种简单而优雅的计划，
again that's like a sort of
straightforward elegant plan but
显然很慢
obviously potentially very slow
这将我们带入下一个主题，即日志压缩和快照，以及
which brings us to the next topic which
is log compaction and and snapshots and
这与实验3b有很大关系，实际上您会看到日志压缩和
this has a lot to do with lab 3b
actually you'll see log compaction and
实验室3b中vlog 3b中的快照，以及日志压缩和
snapshots in vlog 3b in lab 3b and so
the problem that log compaction and
快照解决了一个难题，对于一个长期运行的系统，
snapshotting is solving a raft is that
indeed for a long-running system that's
如果已经按照图2的规则进行了数周，数月或数年，
been going for weeks or months or years
if we just follow the figure 2 rules the
日志只会持续增长，最终可能会导致数以百万计的条目
log just keeps on growing may end up you
know millions and millions of entries
很长，因此如果将其存储在磁盘上，例如
long and so requires a lot of memory to
store if you store it on disk like if
您必须在每次保存日志时都保存它，它消耗了我
you have to persist it every time you
persist the log it's using up a huge I
可能在磁盘上没有空间，并且如果服务器曾经启动过，它必须重建其
may not space on disk and if a server
ever be starts it has to reconstruct its
通过从以下位置重放这些数百万个日志条目来表示状态
state by replaying these millions and
millions of log entries from the very
开始，整个服务器可能需要几个小时才能运行
beginning which could take like hours
for a server to run through its entire
日志，如果它崩溃并重新启动，我们将执行所有类似的操作
log and we execute it if it crashes and
restarts all of which is like similar
浪费什么，因为在崩溃之前它已经有应用程序
what kind of wasted because before it
crashed it had already had applications
状态，因此为了应对这种愤怒，请使用快照和
state and so in order to cope with this
wrath has this idea of snapshots and the
快照背后的一种想法是能够保存或要求应用程序
sort of idea behind snapshots is to be
able to save or ask the application to
保存其状态的副本以及特定的日志条目，因此我们
save a copy of its state as of a
particular log entry so we've been
大多数情况下是忽略应用程序，但事实是您知道我们是否拥有
mostly kind of ignoring the application
but the fact is that you know if we have
假设我们正在BRAF下构建键值存储，您知道日志是
a suppose we're building a key value
store under BRAF you know the log is
将包含一堆您知道放入获取或读写请求的信息
gonna contain a bunch of you know
putting gets or read and write request
所以也许某条法律包含您知道某客户希望将X设置为一个的看跌期权
so maybe a law contains you know a put
that some client wants to set X to one
然后是另一个，它说X到2，然后您知道y等于7或
and then another one where it says X to
2 and then you know y equals 7 or
无论如何，如果在筏执行时没有崩溃，
whatever and if there's no crashes as
the raft is executing along there's
如果是Rath上方的图层，将是这个应用程序，
going to be this if the layer above Rath
there's going to be this application and
应用程序，如果它是键值存储数据库，它将要满足
the application if it's a key value
store databases it's going to be meeting
这张桌子，筏子在我们下一张桌子后递给它一个命令
this table and as raft hands it one
command after our next
应用程序将更新其表，以便您在第一个之后知道
the applications going to update its
table so you know after the first
命令将X设置为1，第二条命令稳定后
command it's going to set X to one and
it's stable after the second command
它会更新它的表，你知道
it's going to update its table you know
一个有趣的事实是，对于大多数应用程序，应用程序状态为
one interesting fact is that for most
applications the application state is
在某种程度上可能比相应的日志小得多
likely to be much smaller than the
corresponding log right at some level we
知道您知道的日志和状态就是其中的日志，并且
know that the the you know the log and
the state are the log in that and the
日志中某些点的状态都是可互换的，它们都
state as of some point in the log are
kind of interchangeable right they both
关于应用程序状态的某种暗示是相同的，但是日志可能
sort of implied the same thing about the
state of the application but the log may
包含很多人，他们知道很多多重作业2x他们用尽了
contain a lot of you know a lot of
multiple assignments 2x they use up a
日志中有很多空间，但也可以有效地将其压缩为单个
lot of space in the log but are also to
effectively compact it down to a single
表中的条目，这在这些复制的应用程序中非常典型
entry in the table and that's pretty
typical of these replicated applications
但关键是我们没有存储可能会非常庞大​​的日志，
but the point is that instead of storing
the log which may go to be huge we have
而是选择存储可能较小的表的选项，这是
the option of storing instead the table
which might be a lot smaller and that's
当筏感觉到日志已经到达时，快照正在执行什么操作
what the snapshots are doing so when
raft feels that it's log has gotten to
太大，您知道的大小超过一兆字节或十兆字节
be too large you know more than a
megabyte or ten megabytes or whatever
一些任意的限制筏将要求应用程序制作快照
some arbitrary limit raft will ask the
application to take make a snapshot of
它在日志中某个点的应用程序状态
it the application state as of a certain
point in the log
因此，如果我们添加了筏是否要求应​​用程序提供快照引用，
so if we add if raft asked the
application for a snapshot reference it
会在快照中选择快照所引用的一点，并要求
would pick a point in the log that the
snapshot referred to and require the
产生快照的应用程序，这是非常关键的
application to produce a snapshot as at
that point this is extremely critical
因为因为我们要做的是在那之前扔掉所有东西
because the because what we're about to
do is throw away everything before that
点，所以如果没有意愿去寻找与快照相对应的点
point so if there's not a will to find
point that corresponds to a snapshot
那么我们就无法安全地丢弃该点之前的日志，这意味着
then we can't safely throw away the log
before that point so that means that
拉斯（Rath）是否会让您知道要在按扣上扣一下，所以基本上
Rath is gonna have you know ask for
snaps on the snap so it's basically just
该表只是关于数据库服务器的，我们还需要注释
the table it's just about a database
server and we also need to annotate the
快照，其中的条目号与您相对应，因此基本上就是您
snapshot with the entry number that are
corresponds to you so it's basically you
知道条目是否为1 2 3此快照对应于日志之后
know if the entries are 1 2 3 this
snapshot corresponds to just after log
如果我们将快照持久化到磁盘大鼠持久化，则快照在手的索引3
index 3 with the snapshot in hand
if we persist it to disk rats persistent
到磁盘筏不再需要这部分日志，它可以简单地抛出
to disk raft never again will need this
part of the logs and it can simply throw
只要它保留了债务日志中某个快照的快照，它就会消失
it away as long as it persists a
snapshot as of a certain in debt log
索引加上该索引之后的日志，只要它一直保留在磁盘上
index plus the log after that index as
long as that's persisted to disk we
从来不需要之前进行记录，所以这就是英国皇家空军所做的一切
never going to need to log before that
and so this is what RAF does the rocks
要求应用程序获取快照，然后将快照保存到磁盘
ask the application for snapshot gets
the snapshot saves it to disk with the
记录之后，它会立即将此记录扔掉，因此它确实可以运行
log after that it just throws away this
log here right and so it really operates
或那种持久性故事都是关于日志中的快照对
or the sort of persistence story is all
about pairs of a snapshot in the log
之后，与快照关联的日志中的点之后，我看不到
after that after the point in the log
associated with snapshot I don't see
这是
this yes
不，它仍然是，这是您知道的一种幻像条目，一二
no it's still it's it's you know there's
these sort of phantom entries one two
三，您知道日志的后缀确实被视为仍然是
three and this you know suffix of the
log is indeed viewed as still the it's
也许思考它的正确方法仍然只有一个日志，除了这些
maybe the right way to think of it is
still there's just one log except these
条目是一种幻像条目，我们可以将其视为
entries are sort of phantom entries that
we that we can view as being kind of
原则上在那里，但由于我们是我们，所以我们无需查看它们，因为我们
there in principle but since we're we
never need to look at them because we
具有快照的事实是它们只是碰巧没有存储在任何地方
have the snapshot the fact that they
just happened not to be stored anywhere
既不在这里也不在那里，但是，是的，你应该认为它是
is neither here nor there but it's but
yeah you should think of it as being
窃取了相同的日志，这不仅是丢弃了他们的早期条目，还这样做了
stole the same log it's just not just
threw away their early entries did this
答案可能有点太客气了，因为事实是
that's a maybe a little bit too glib of
an answer because the fact is that
图二以有关日志的方式进行讨论，使您可以按照以下方式进行操作：
figure two talks about the log in ways
that makes it that if you just follow
有时候您仍然需要这些较早的条目，因此您必须
figure to you sometimes still need these
earlier entries and so you'll have to
考虑到有时它说：
reinterpret figure two a little bit in
light of the fact that sometimes it says
等等等等日志条目不存在的地方
blah blah blah a log entry where the log
entry doesn't exist okay
好的，那么重启时会发生什么，所以重启的故事要多一些
okay and so what happens on a restart
so the restart story is a little more
它比以前仅带有一个日志要复杂得多
complicated in it than it used to be
with just a log what happens on a
重新启动是，筏子需要离开，以提供最新的图形
restart is that there needs to be away
for raft to give the latest for graph to
在其磁盘上找到最新的快照日志对，并将快照交给
find the latest snapshot log pair on its
disk and hand the snapshot to the
应用程序，因为我们不再能够重播您知道的所有日志
application because we no longer are
able to replay you know all the log
条目，因此必须有其他方法可以基本上初始化应用程序
entries so there must be some other way
to initialize the application basically
应用程序不仅必须能够生成快照
not only is the application have to be
able to produce a snapshot of
应用程序状态，但它必须能够吸收以前制作的
application state but but it has to be
able to absorb a previously made
快照并从快照等方式将其稳定地重建在内存中
snapshot and sort of reconstruct it
stable in memory from a snapshot and so
现在，即使筏可以管理整个快照内容
this now even though raft is kind of
managing this whole snapshotting stuff
快照内容实际上是应用程序和RAF的属性
the snapshot contents are really the
property to the application and RAF
甚至不了解其中的内容，只有应用程序可以理解，因为它
doesn't even understand what's in here
only the application does because it's
全部包含应用程序特定信息，因此重新启动后
all full of application specific
information so after a restart the
应用程序必须能够吸收筏发现的最新快照，因此
application has to be able to absorb the
latest snapshot that raft found so for
就这么简单，不幸的是，快照和
just this simple it would be simple
unfortunately this snapshotting and in
特别是领导者可能会丢弃部分日志的想法
particular the idea that the leader
might throw away part of its log
引入了一个主要的复杂性，那就是如果有一些
introduces a major piece of complexity
and that is that if there's some
跟随者，其日志在领导者登录之前结束
follower out there whose log ends before
the point at which the leaders log
然后开始，除非我们发明新东西，否则需要安装monney快照
starts then unless we invent something
new we need monney install snapshot
除非我们发明新东西，否则追随者永远无法掌握最新信息
unless we invent something new that
follower can never get up-to-date right
因为如果关注者知道是否有一些关注者，其日志仅为
because if the followers you know if
there's some follower whose log only is
前两个日志条目我们不再需要三个日志条目
the first two log entries we no longer
have the log entry three that's required
在附加条目RPC中将其发送给该关注者，以使其日志赶上
to send it to that follower in an append
entries RPC to allow its log to catch up
对于领导者，我们现在可以避免
to the leaders now
we could avoid this problem by having
如果有任何追随者，领导者永远不会删除其日志的一部分
the leader never drop part of its log if
there's any follower out there that
还没有赶上领导者正在考虑做一个
hasn't caught up to the point at which
the leader is thinking about doing a
快照，因为领导者知道下一个索引
snapshot because the leader knows
through next index
其实领导者并不真正知道，但领导者原则上可以知道
well actually leader doesn't really know
but the leader could know in principle
每个追随者走了多远，领导者就可以说我永远不会
how far each follower had gotten and the
leader could say well I'm just never
要在最短的关注者结束之前删除我的日志部分
gonna drop the part of my log before the
end of the follower with the shortest
日志，这没关系，他们实际上可能只是个好主意。
log and that would be okay they might
actually just be a good idea period the
为什么这不是一个好主意的原因当然是如果一个追随者
reason why that's maybe not such a great
idea is that of course if a follower
关闭一周，您就会知道不会确认日志条目，并且
shut down for a week you know it's not
gonna be acknowledging log entries and
这意味着领导者无法通过快照减少内存使用，因此
that means that the leader can't reduce
its memory use by snapshotting so the
选择的木筏设计方式是允许首领扔掉
way the raft designs chosen to go is
that the leader is allowed to throw away
某些追随者需要的部分日志，因此我们需要一些
parts of its logs that would be needed
by some follower and so we need some
追加条目以处理某些结尾之间的差距的其他方案
other scheme that append entries to deal
with the gap between the end of some
关注者登录领导者日志的开头，因此解决方案是
followers log in the beginning of the
leaders log and so that solution is the
安装快照RPC的方法是，当一个领导者时，我们会有一些跟随者
install snapshot RPC and the deal is
that when a leader we have some follower
谁的日志是，您知道刚刚打开日志，那么领导者将
whose log is that you know just powered
on its log as short the leaders gonna
发送并附加条目，您知道它将被强迫领导者
send it and append entries and you know
it's gonna be forced the leaders gonna
被迫备份，并且有时领导者知道失败或失败
be forced to backup and at some point
the leader you know failure or fail
依赖召回将使领导者意识到这已经到了开始
dependent recalls will cause the leader
to realize it it's reached the beginning
实际日志的门，然后在该位置发送而不是附加
of the actual log its doors and at that
point instead of sending in append
领导者将发送其当前快照的条目以及当前法律以及其发送的
entries the leader will send its current
snapshot plus current law well send its
当前快照给关注者，然后大概立即关注它
current snapshot to the follower and
then presumably immediately follow it
附有符合领导者现行法律的附加条目
with an append entries that has the
leaders current law
问题
questions
是的，我很伤心，这就像在这里增加了很大的复杂性
yeah I'm the sad truth this is like this
is adds significant complexity here
Jarrell我今年三岁，部分原因是因为需要这种合作
Jarrell I'm three partially because of
the kind of cooperation that's required
在拉夫之间，这有点违反模块化
between raff this is sort of a little
bit of a violation of modularity it
需要良好的合作，例如安装快照时
requires a good deal cooperation like
for example when an install snapshot
进入了筏，但筏确实需要应用程序
comes in it's delivered to raft but raft
really requires the application to
吸收快照，因此他们彼此之间要比其他人更多地交谈
absorb the snapshot so they have to talk
to each other more than they otherwise
可能是的问题是，这是创建快照的方式
might yes the question is that this is
the way the snapshot is created
完全取决于应用程序，因此快照
dependent on the application
it's absolutely it so the snapshot
创建功能是应用程序的一部分，就像钥匙一样
creation function is part of the
application as part of like the key
价值服务器，所以抽奖您知道如何以某种方式调用应用程序并说geez
value server so raffle you know somehow
call up to the application and say geez
您知道我现在真的很喜欢应用程序中的快照，因为只有
you know I really like a snapshot right
now in the application because only the
应用程序了解其状态，并且您知道反函数
application understands what it's status
and you know the inverse function by
应用程序也可以完全从快照文件重建状态
which an application reconstructs a
state from a snapshot files also totally
当然，取决于每个应用程序在哪里交织在一起
application dependent where there's
intertwining because of course every
快照必须在日志中标有与之对应的点
snapshot has to be labeled with a point
in a log that it corresponds to
谈论第六条法则和十三条图，好吧，这里的问题
talking about rule six and figure
thirteen okay so yeah the question here
就是这样，您将在实验三中面临这个问题，因为RPC系统
is that and you will be faced with this
in lab three that because the RPC system
并非完全可靠且序列不正确，RBC可能无法
isn't perfectly reliable and perfectly
sequenced and RBC's can arrive out of
是否订购，或者您可能发送RPC并没有得到任何答复，并认为是
order or not at all or you may send an
RPC and get no response and think it was
丢失，但实际上已传递，并且丢失了所有这些回复
lost but actually was delivered and was
the reply that was lost all these things
发生包括将我们的个人电脑和领导者发送到任何安装快照的情况
happen including to send to whatever
install snapshot our pcs and the leaders
几乎可以肯定，我们同时发送了许多PC，您都知道
almost certainly sending out many our
pcs concurrently you know both append
条目和安装快照，这意味着您可以获取诸如install之类的信息
entries and install snapshots that means
that you can get things like install
回顾过去的电脑
snapshot our pcs from deep in the past
几乎所有其他权利，因此追随者必须小心
almost anything else right and therefore
the the follower has to be careful you
知道必须仔细考虑到达的安装快照，并且
know has to think carefully about an
install snapshot that arrives and the
是的，我想您要问的是，跟随者是否收到
yeah I think the specific thing you're
asking is that if follower receives that
看起来完全冗余的安装快照，即安装
an install snapshot that appears to be
completely redundant that is the install
快照包含的信息早于关注者的信息
snapshot contains information that's
older than the information the follower
已经有了追随者应该做什么，并统治了第六条
already has
what should the follower do and rule six
图十三说了些什么，但我认为对此的同样有效的回应是
and figure thirteen says something but I
think equally valid response to that is
追随者可以忽略明显不是过去的快照
that the follower can ignore a snapshot
that clearly is from the past I don't
非常了解第六条规则，我想继续讲一些
really understand that rule six okay I
want to move on to sort of somewhat more
到目前为止，我们还没有真正尝试确定概念性话题
conceptual topic for a bit so far we
haven't really tried to nail down
关于什么是正确的一切
anything about what it meant to be
correct
我对复制服务的含义已经是任何其他类型的服务
what I meant for a replicated service
already any other kind of service to be
行为正确，原因以及您对我大多数人都知道
behaving correctly and the reason why
and you know whatever for most of my
我设法过上的生活而不必太担心精确
life I managed to get by without
worrying too much about precise
正确性的定义，但事实是您知道您是否要尝试
definitions of correctness but the fact
is that you know if you're trying to
优化某些东西，或者您尝试通过一些奇怪的极端情况进行思考
optimize something or you're trying to
think through some weird corner case
实际上有一个或多或少正式的决定方法通常是很方便的
it's often handy to actually have a more
or less formal way of deciding is that
行为正确与否，所以您知道我们在说什么
behavior correct or not correct and so
you know for here what we're talking
您是否知道客户正在将请求发送到我们复制的
about is you know clients are sending in
requests to the to our replicated
使用我们的PC进行服务，也许他们会派人知道该服务，也许是
service with our PC maybe they'll be
sending who knows well maybe the service
崩溃了，它可能正在启动，您知道正在加载快照或任何客户端
is crash it can be starting and you know
loading snapshots or whatever the client
发送请求并获得响应，例如响应正确吗？
sends in a request and gets a response
like is that response correct how are we
应该如何判断响应a是正确的还是
supposed to how are we supposed to tell
whether response a would be correct or
回应B，所以我们需要一个概念，我们需要一个相当正式的区分概念
response B so we need a notion we need a
pretty formal notion of distinguishing
哦，从现在开始还可以，这是一个错误的答案，对于本练习，我们
oh that's okay from now that would be a
wrong answer and for this lab the our
正确性的概念是线性化能力，我提到了强
notion of correctness is linearize
ability and I mentioned strong
一致性，我提到的一些论文具有很强的一致性和
consistency and some of the papers I
mentioned strong consistency and
基本等同于线性化能力线性化能力是一种
basically equivalent to linearize
ability linearize ability is a sort of a
形式化或多或少的行为，如果有
formalization of more or less of the
behavior you would expect if there was
只是一台服务器，并且没有崩溃，它执行了客户端请求的命令
just one server and it didn't crash and
it executed the command client requests
一次只有一个，您知道没有发生过什么有趣的事，所以它有一个
one at a time and you know nothing funny
ever happened so it has it has a
定义和定义我会写出定义然后再讨论
definition and the definition I'll write
out the definition then talk about it so
因此执行历史记录是可线性化的，可线性化，这在注释中
so an execution history is linearizable
linearizable and this is in the notes if
存在总订单，因此执行历史记录是一个序列
there exists a total order so an
execution history is a sequence of
客户请求也许来自许多客户的许多请求
client requests maybe many requests from
many clients
如果历史记录中有一些总的操作顺序，则它与
if there's some total order of the
operations in the history it matches the
请求的实时顺序，因此如果有一个请求
real-time order of requests so if one
request
如果客户发出请求并得到响应，然后再及时
if client sends out a request and gets a
response and then later in time another
客户端发出一个请求，我得到响应，这两个请求已排序
client sends out a request and I get a
response those two requests are ordered
因为其中一个在另一个完成之后开始
because one of them's started after the
other one finished
所以它的线性化历史是线性化的，如果存在一个阶
so it's linearizable history is
linearizable if there exists an order of
历史记录中与非并发实时匹配的操作
the operations in the history that
matches real-time for non concurrent
要求没有时间重叠的请求，每次阅读都可以
requests that is for a request to didn't
overlap in time and each read you can
认为它是每个读取都从最前面的值看到的值
think of it as each read sees the value
from the most immediately preceding
顺序访问同一条数据的最新权利
right to the the same piece of data most
recent right in the order all right this
这个定义让我通过示例来说明它的含义
is the definition let me illustrate what
it means by running through an example
因此，历史记录首先是客户操作的记录，所以这是一个
so first of all the history is a record
of client operations so this is a
您可以从此定义之外应用的定义并不有吸引力
definition that you can apply from
outside this definition doesn't appeal
以任何方式了解实施内部发生的情况或实施的方式
in any way to what happens inside the
implementation or how the implementation
如果我们看到系统正在运行并且可以观察的话，那是可以做到的
works it's something that we can if we
see a system operating and we can watch
传入和传出的消息我们可以回答的问题是执行
the messages that come in and out we can
answer the question was that execution
我们观察到线性化，所以让我
that we observe linearizable so let me
让我写出历史，并讨论为什么它是线性化的或不可线性化的
let me write out of history and talk
about why it is or isn't linearizable
好的，这是一个示例，新的眼睛功能谈到了操作
从一个点开始，到另一个点结束，所以这对应于
start at one point and end at another
and so this corresponds to the time at
哪个客户发送了一个请求，然后又收到了回复，所以让我们假设
which a client sends a request and then
later receives a reply so let us suppose
我们的历史表明，在这个特定时间的某个客户
that our history says that at at some
particular time this time some client
发送了对名为X的数据项的写入请求，并要求将其设置为1
然后时间过去了，第二个竖线是该客户获得
and then time passed and at the second
vertical bar is when that client got a
此时通过发送请求进行回复，您知道时间过去，谁知道
reply through send a request at this
point you know time pass who knows
当客户在那里收到回复，然后稍后及时
what's happening when the client got a
reply there and then later in time that
客户或其他客户并不重要
client or some other client doesn't
really matter
再次发送对项目X和值2的写入请求，并获得响应
正确，与此同时，一些客户端发送对X的读取并获得值2并发送了
right meanwhile some client sends a read
for X and gets value 2 and sent the
在那里请求并获得值为2的响应，还有另一个
request there and got the response with
value 2 there and there's another
请求我们观察到它是历史记录的一部分已发送给阅读
request that we observed it's a part of
the history request was sent to read
值X并返回值1，所以当我们有这样的历史记录时，您
value X and it got value 1 back and so
when we have a history like this you
知道问题是您问这个历史的吗？
know the question were that you asked
about this history is is this a
机械化服务做系统的线性化历史
linearizable history that is did the
machinery did the service did the system
产生了这个历史，是线性化的系统还是它产生了
that produced this history and was that
a linearizable system or did it produce
在这种情况下，如果此历史不是线性听不见的，则为可线性化的历史
a linearizable history in this case if
this history is not linear inaudible
然后丽莎，我们在谈论我有3个，我们知道那里有一个问题
then then Lisa we're talking about I
have 3 we know we have a problem there
必须是一些可以的错误，所以我们需要对此进行分析，以确定是否
must be some some bug ok so we need to
analyze this to figure out if it's
线性化的线性化能力要求我们产生一个订单
linearizable there's linear linearize
ability requires us to produce an order
您知道该历史中四个操作的一个顺序，所以我们知道
you know one by one order of the four
operations in that history so we know
我们正在寻找订单，并且有两个约束
we're looking for an order and there's
two constraints on the
命令之一是，如果一项操作在另一项操作开始之前完成，则该操作
order one is if one operation finished
before another started then the one that
首先完成必须在历史上排在第一位，另一个是如果有人看过
finished first has to come first in the
history the other is if some read sees a
特定的写入值，则读取必须按顺序在写入之后进行
particular written value then the read
must come after the write in the order
好吧，我们要订购，所以我们要产生一个有四个订单
all right so we want to order so we're
gonna produce an order that has four
输入两个权利和两个线索，我将用箭头画出
entries the two rights and the two leads
I'm gonna draw with arrows that
这两个规则所暗示的约束，那么我们的命令就必须服从
constraints implied by those two rules
and then our order is gonna have to obey
这些约束，所以一个约束是此写操作在此之前完成
these constraints so one constraint is
that this write finished before this
写操作开始，因此排序约束之一是该写操作
write started and therefore one of the
ordering constraints is that this write
必须以总顺序出现，在此写入之前，此读取看到了
must appear in the total order before
this write this read saw the value of
所以总阅读顺序必须是两个
two so in the total order the most
recent right that this read must come
在此权利之后，此写入必须是最新的权利，这意味着
after this right and this write must be
the most recent right so that means that
按照总顺序，我们必须看到X-2的右边，然后在它后面读取X
in the total order we must see the right
of X - 2 and then after it the read of X
它产生-如果我们假设X尚未读取，则X的读数为1
it yields - and this this read of X of 1
if we assume that the X didn't already
值1一定存在这种关系，那就是读取
have the value 1 there there must be in
this relationship and that is the read
必须紧随权利之后，并且此权利也必读
must come after the right and this read
also must become for this right and
也许还有其他限制-无论如何我们都可以接受
maybe there's some other restrictions -
anyway we can take these we can take
这组箭头并将其展平成一个顺序，实际上如此
this set of arrows and flatten it out
into an order and that actually works so
该订单即表明该历史记录的总订单
the order that's the total order that
demonstrates that this history is
linearizable首先是x-1的右边，然后是x的读数产生1，然后是
linearizable is first the right of x - 1
then the read of x yielding 1 then the
x-2的右边和x的读数产生2
right of x - 2 and the read of x that
yields 2
好吧，所以这个命令确实遵守命令
alright so the fact that there is this
order that does obey the ordering
约束条件表明该历史记录是线性化能力，您不知道吗
constraints shows that this history is
linearize ability and doesn't you know
如果我们担心产生此历史的系统是否
if we're worried about the system that
produced this history whether it's a but
该系统是线性的，那么我们看到的这个特定示例没有
that system is linearizable then this
particular example we saw it doesn't
与该系统可线性化的任何假设相矛盾
contradict the presumption that the
system is linearizable any questions
关于我每次读取时看到的内容，您知道读取X时所看到的值必须是
about what I just did each read sees you
know read of X the value it sees must be
它们按顺序按最近的程序正确编写的值，因此
them value written by the most the most
recent proceeding right in the order so
您知道在这种情况下，我们完全可以接受此订单，因为
you know in this case in this case we're
totally ok with this order because this
读取它看到的值确实是最近一次写入所写入的值
read the value it saw is indeed the
value written by the most recent write
按照这个顺序，这读了它感叹的价值，我的意思是非正式地
in this order and this read the value it
sighs I mean in informally it's that
如果我在Rita中写了一些东西，那么不能真正读的读取就不会产生过时的数据
reads can't real should not be yielding
stale data if I write something in Rita
回到天哪，我应该看到我写的值，这就像
back gosh I should see the value I wrote
and that's like a formalization of the
认为
notion that
哦，是的，是的，好吧，让我，让我，他说对了，这不是
oh yes oh yeah yeah all right let me let
me he's right up example that's not
确实是线性化的，因此示例二让我们假设我们的历史是我们有权
indeed linearizable so example two let's
suppose our history is we had a right of
X值为一，右为第二
X value one right back with value two
所以我们也想写出箭头，所以我们知道
and so this one we also want to write
out the arrows and so we know what the
约束在任何总阶上，我们可能会发现X的权利为1，因为
constraints are on any total order we
might find the right of X to one because
之所以需要时间，是因为它是在正确的x开始之前实时完成的，并且必须
of time because it finished in real time
before the right x to started and must
在以任何令人满意的顺序出现之前，我们必须产生Ecsta的权利，两个必须
come before in any satisfying order we
produce the right of Ecsta two has to
出现在X的读取之前就在右边，它产生两个，所以我们有这个箭头
come before the right before the read of
X that yields two so we have this arrow
X的读取必须在X到1的读取开始之前完成，所以我们有了这个
the read of X had to finished before the
read of X to one started so we have this
箭头和X读为1，因为它看到值1必须在
arrow and the read of X to one because
it saw value one has to come after the
X-1的权利，更重要的是X 2的权利-更重要的是，我们不能
right of X - 1 and more crucially before
the right of X 2 - right so we can't
如果先紧跟着X，我将写出X
have this read of X yielding one if it's
immediately preceded by I'll write out X
-2所以我们也有这样的箭头，因为其中有一个循环
- 2 so we also have this arrow like this
and because there's a cycle in these
约束没有可以遵循所有这些约束的命令，因此
constraints there's no order that can
obey all these constraints and therefore
这个历史不是线性化的，因此产生它的系统是
this history is not linearizable and so
the system that produced it is
不是一个线性化的系统，您知道历史将是线性化的
is not a linearizable system you know
would be linearizable the history was
缺少这三个中的任何一个，我会中断周期，是的，也许我不是
missing any one of these three and I
would break the cycle yes maybe I'm not
可以肯定，因为假设还是我不知道如何合并像这样的非常奇怪的东西
sure because suppose or I don't know how
to incorporate very strange things like
假设某人为红色27，您知道如果没有27的权利并不是真的
supposing somebody red 27 you know it
doesn't really if there's no right of 27
读27至少不会像我写出规则那样排序
a read of 27 doesn't at least the way
I've written out the rules doesn't sort
当然，您可能会构建某种反依赖性
of well there may be some sort of anti
dependency that you would construct okay
嗯，下周我将继续讨论
um I will continue this discussion next
week